Okay, I'm going to lay this exactly on here where we want it, and kind of hold on a little bit.
We flipped it, and now we can put the shelf back, like that.
Okay.
Now, here's the part where we're going to peel it back, and what I'm letting the cracker known here is that I need him to let go.
Doing a little spiritual work on my cracker.
Everybody's a healer in Sedona.
Okay, so we're going to start work.
We'll see if it comes off here.
And there we go; it's coming off nicely.
Oh, that's pretty good.
You see what I'm doing here?
When it starts to come up on the wax paper you just kind of press it down a little more.
I mean, look at this.
Wow.
That's nice.
Wow, I haven't had one work that easily ever, and that's in front of the camera.
Nice.
Okay, we're going to show you what this looks like.
And this is our chocolate cracker.
And as I said, I don't use oil.
There was a raw cracker that I tried recently, and it was kind of a crepe, and it had oil in it, and it's just not my preference.
So, if that doesn't bother you, some of us are very sensitive to oils.
When I consume oils, I try to have them in the food that they're in.
So that would be an avocado, or nuts, or a coconut, but separated oils have to be really careful with for me personally.
So, look at how beautiful this is without any oil at all.
And of course we used the coconut butter that was a lot of the oil.
We have nuts in there, and we have the flax, and that kept it together beautifully.
And now we're going to go over to the dehydrator.